let quiz=[
{
  question: " The 2004 Olympics were held in :",
  option: [
       "Bangkok ",
       "Rome ",
       "Athens",
       "Nagasaki",
  ],
  answer: 3,
},
{
  question: "Twenty-20 matches are played in the game of ",
  option: [
       "Hockey",
       "Football",
       "Badminton",
       "Cricket",
  ],
  answer: 4,
},
{
  question: "Arjuna Award was introduced in",
  option: [
       "1961",
       "1969",
       "1972",
       "1995",
  ],
   answer: 1,
},
{
  question: "How many gold medals have been won by India in the Olympics till 2020?",
  option: [
       "24",
       "26",
       "28",
       "20",
  ],
  answer: 3,
},
{
  question: "Wankhede Stadium is situated in :",
  option: [
       "chandigarh",
       "Jaipur",
       "Mumbai",
       "kolkata",
  ],
  answer: 3,
},
{
  question: "In which of the following Hindi film has actor Shahrukh Khan played the role of a Hockey Coach? ",
  option: [
       "Guru",
       "Chak De India",
       "Om Shanti Om",
       "Jab We Met",
  ],
  answer: 2,
},
{
  question: "Netaji Subhash National Institute of Sports is located at :",
  option: [
       "Kolkata",
       "New Delhi",
       "Jhansi",
       "Patiala",
  ],
  answer: 4,
},
{
  question: "Saina Nehwal is related with which among the following sports ?",
  option: [
       "Badminton",
       "Tennis",
       "Chess",
       "Table Tennis",
  ],
  answer: 1,
},
{
  question: "The Asian Games were held in Delhi for the first time in...?",
  option: [
       "1951",
       "1963",
       "1971",
       "1982",
  ],
  answer: 1,
},
{
  question: "The 'Dronacharya Award' is given to...?",
  option: [
       "Sportsmen",
       "Coach",
       "Umpires",
       "Sports Ediotrs",
  ],
  answer: 2 ,
},
{
  question: "The Olympic Games are normally held at an interval of ...",
  option: [
  "2 years",
  "3 years",
  "4 years",
  "5 years",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "Who is the first Indian Woman to win an Asian Games gold in 400 m run ?",
  option: [
  "M.L. Valsamma",
  "P.T. Usha",
  "Kamaljit Sandhu",
  "K.Malleshwari",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
{
  question: "Who of the following is a Football Player ?",
  option: [
  "Fernando Alonso",
  "Kimi Raikkonen",
  "Lewis Hamilton",
  "Nicolas Anelka",
  ],
  answer: 4, 
},
{
  question: "What is Tiger Woods( A golf player ) real first name ?",
  option: [
  "Eldrick",
  "Jhon",
  "Thomson",
  "Nick",
  ],
  answer: 1, 
},
{
  question: "What is the maximum amount of time allowed to look for a lost ball ? ",
  option: [
  "5 minutes",
  "2 minutes",
  "3 minutes",
  "6 minutes",
  ],
  answer: 3, 
},
]

